

## Contact

#### **Phone**

+48 571 360 043

#### **Email**

wjezierski23@gmail.com

#### **Portfolio**

https://wjezierski.com

#### **Github**

https://github.com/Wojciech-Jezierski

#### Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wojciechjezierski-dev

## **Skills**

- **HTML**
- CSS, SCSS, BEM, CSS Modules
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React, Redux
- React-query, React-hook-form, React-router-dom
- Tailwind CSS, Material UI, **Styled Components**
- REST API, GraphQL API
- **End-to-end tests in Cypress**
- Firebase, Chart.js
- Docker, CI/CD Pipelines (basics)
- NPM, Yarn, ESLint, Husky
- Figma, Adobe XD
- Scrum, Jira
- **GIT**

## Languages

- Polish native
- English upper intermediate (B2)

# Wojciech Jezierski

## Junior Front-end developer

## About me

Computer Science graduate with 6 months of commercial experience as (Junior) Front-end Developer. Proficient in implementation of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with an aim to transform design concepts into responsive and visually appealing websites and applications. Creative problem solver with a passion for creating user-friendly and engaging web interfaces. Excited about an opportunity to further develop in front-end or transfer my skills into the new role.

## **Work Experience**

O Northvolt Systems Sp. z o.o.

06.2022 - 10.2022

## Front-end developer (internship)

- · Developed front-end segments of the Manufacturing Execution System (MES) in the
- Created reusable and responsive views for multiple systems
- Presented data using a chart with the adoption of the Chart.js library and the Vue.js framework
- · Reporting in Jira
- Cooperated within an international team in the Scrum methodology

Technologies: Vue.js, Chart.js, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, HTML, CSS, Jira

05.2021 - 08.2021

- Front-end developer (practice)
- UX/UI prototyping of a web application • Created websites in WordPress
- Managed selection and configuration of appropriate WordPress plugins

Technologies: PHP, Wordpress, Figma, Adobe XD

## **Completed projects**

#### HR Dashboard (Mentoring Reskilled - https://reskilled.io/)

- This is an HR data collection/management platform which allows HR representatives to process job postings and applicants' data
- The project was written in TypeScript and the React framework, which uses hooks
- It has a full CRUD including JWT tokens and the API documentation in Swagger
- The following libraries were used: Tailwind UI styling; Yup form validation; React-hook-form - form handling; Axios and React-query - API communication
- Created additional GET Endpoint as JSON object functionality with mockup in designer.mocky.io
- Employee of the month functionality is displayed through Graphql-request and React-query libraries
- Functionality has been tested using End-to-end tests in Cypress
- The project was carried out under the oversight of a senior software engineer and subsequent parts were subject to senior code review

### Live track app (Engineering Thesis)

• This is an application for forwarders (logistics), developed using firebase platform, Google Maps API, React framework and SCSS

#### **Expense tracker**

· This is an application for expense tracking, written in plain JavaScript and React, using hooks (UseState, useContext, useReducer) and the context API

## **Education**

O 03.2023 - Present

WSB University in Gdańsk

MSc - Management of IT projects and services

10.2019 - 02.2023

WSB University in Gdańsk

**BEng - Computer Science**